A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, President, Detlev Bronk, Personal and Professional papers FA965
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Personal and professional papers
  - Speaking Engagements, 1933-1952
    - United States Department of Agriculture, UNESCO, Declination, 1946 (Box 71, Folder 40)
    - Speaking Engagement, Princeton University Bicentennial, 1947 February 21-23 (Box 71, Folder 41)
    - Serving Through Science, Radio Series, 1946-1947 (Box 71, Folder 42)
    - Mt. Holyoke College, Phi Beta Kappa. Declination, 1946 (Box 71, Folder 43)
    - Speaking Engagement, American Philosophical Society, 1947 April (Box 71, Folder 44)
    - Speaking Engagement, Peripatetic Society, Hospital of the University of PA, 1947 February 7-8 (Box 71, Folder 45)
    - Annals of Internal Medicine, Article, 1947 April (Box 71, Folder 46)
    - American Scientist, Article, 1946 June (Box 71, Folder 47)
    - Journal of Neurophysiology, Article, 1947 March (Box 71, Folder 48)
    - Speaking Engagement, Rockford College, Centennial Science Conference, 1947 February 23 (Box 71, Folder 49)
    - Speaking Engagement, Columbia University, Sigma Xi, 1947 May 6 (Box 71, Folder 50)
    - Bronk Lectures in Norway and Sweden, 1947-1948 (Box 71, Folder 51)
    - Speaking Engagement, Quartermaster Association; Northwestern University - Century Fund Series, 1948 (Box 71, Folder 52)
    - Speaking Engagement, Los Angeles Academy of Medicine, 1948 January (Box 71, Folder 53)
    - Medical Physics, Article; SE. Princeton University, 1948 (Box 71, Folder 54)
    - SE. University of PA Commencement, 1949 June 15 (Box 71, Folder 55)
    - Speaking Engagement (SE), School District of Philadelphia, Summer workshop, 1948 (Box 71, Folder 56)
    - SE. University of PA Lectures, 1946-1949 (Box 71, Folder 57)
    - Speaking Engagement, Woman's Association of the Baltimore Symphony Orchestra, undated (Box 71, Folder 58)
    - Speaking Engagement, Rice Institute Commencement, 1949 June 3 (Box 71, Folder 59)
    - Speaking Engagement, Middle States Association, 1950 November (Box 71, Folder 60)
    - SE. Phi Beth Kappa, 1950-1951 (Box 71, Folder 61)
    - SE. National Academy of Science Symposium, 1951 (Box 71, Folder 62)
    - Speaking Engagement, National Health Council, 31st Annual Meeting, 1951 April 6 (Box 71, Folder 63)
    - Speaking Engagement, National Wholesale Druggists Association, 1951 October 15 (Box 71, Folder 64)
    - Speaking Engagement, New York University, School of Law, 1951 September 15 (Box 71, Folder 65)
    - Science in Review Television Proaram, 1951 (Box 71, Folder 66)
    - Speaking Engagement, University of California, Scripps Institution of Oceanography, 1951 March 26 (Box 71, Folder 67)
    - Speaking Engagement, Temple University, 50th Anniversary Celebration of the School of Pharmacy, 1951 April 11 (Box 71, Folder 68)
    - Speaking Engagement, Johns Hopkins University, Dedication of Experimental Science Building, 1951 December 7 (Box 71, Folder 69)
    - SE. Queens University, 1952 September 3 (Box 71, Folder 70)
    - Speaking Engagement, U.S. Naval Submarine School, Graduation Exercises, New London, CT, 1951 December 14 (Box 71, Folder 71)
    - Speaking Engagement, Société Philomathique, France; American Philosophical Society, undated (Box 71, Folder 72)
  - Clippings (photocopies), 1920-1963
    - Bronk Clippings, Swarthmore College, 1920 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Bronk Clippings, Education, Symposium of Biophysics, 1934-1937 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1940-1946 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Bronk Clippings, University of PA Bicentennial, 1937-1940 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Bronk Clippings, Science in Progress, 1945 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Telephone Directory, War Department, 1943 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Bronk Clippings, Simon Flexner Memorial, Princeton University Bicentennial Conferences, Miscellaneous, 1946 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Bronk Clippings, Atomic Energy Commission, Princeton Convocation, Miscellaneous, 1947 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1948 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Bronk Clippings, Johns Hopkins University, 1948 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1949 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1949 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Bronk Clippings, Articles, Programs, 1949 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Bronk Clippings, Johns Hopkins, 1949 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Bronk Clippings, Johns Hopkins, 1950 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Bronk Clippings, Johns Hopkins, 1950 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Bronk Clippings, Queen Elizabeth's U.S. Visit, Temple University, Johns Hopkins, National Wholesale Druggists Convention, Miscellaneous, 1951 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Bronk Clippings, Programs, Articles, 1951 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous College Commencement Programs, 1951 (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Bronk Clippings, 1952 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Bronk Clippings, Articles, Programs, 1952 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Bronk Clippings, Appointment to Rockefeller Institute, Miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Bronk Clippings, Astin Case, Miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Bronk Articles and Programs, 1953 (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - Commencement Programs, 1953 (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - Bronk Clippings, Atomic Testing, Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - Bronk Clippings, Atomic Power, Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 72, Folder 27)
    - Bronk Clippings, Programs, Bulletins, 1954 (Box 72, Folder 28)
    - Bronk Clippings, Dr. Robert Oppenheimer, 1954 (Box 72, Folder 29)
    - Bronk Clippings, Satellites, Radiation, 1955 (Box 72, Folder 30)
    - Bronk Clippings, Articles, Bulletins, 1955 (Box 72, Folder 31)
    - Bronk Clippings, United Nations Conference, 1963 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - Honorary Memberships, 1937-1975
    - Academy of Sciences, USSR, 1958-1972 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Belgium Academy of Medicine, 1974-1975 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - French Academy of Sciences, 1952-1975 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Royal Danish Academy, 1956-1975 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - The Royal Institution, 1960-1975 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Royal Society of Arts, 1960-1975 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Royal Society of London, 1948-1960 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Royal Society of London, 1961-1975 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Royal Society of London, Tercentenary, 1958-1964 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Royal Swedish Academy, 1958-1975 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Swiss Academy of Sciences, 1966-1971 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Honorary Degrees, 1937-1970 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - University of Alaska, 1968-1975 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - University of Alaska, 1968-1975 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Alfred University, 1964-1967 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Boston College, 1962 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Brandeis University, 1957-1966 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - University of Brazil, 1958-1974 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - University of Brussels, 1963 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Bucknell University, 1957 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - University of California, 1957-1959 (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Cambridge University, 1956-1964 (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - Columbia University, 1969-1970 (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Dartmouth College, 1956-1969 (Box 73, Folder 24)
    - Georgetown University, 1967 (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - Grinnell, Cincinnati, Tufts, Williams, 1951 (Box 73, Folder 26)
    - Hahnemann Medical College, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 27)
    - Hamilton College, Harvard University, 1953-1961 (Box 73, Folder 28)
    - University of Illinois, 1963 (Box 73, Folder 29)
    - Jefferson Medical College, 1959 (Box 73, Folder 30)
    - Karolinska Institute, Sweden, 1956 (Box 73, Folder 31)
    - Kenyon College, 1951-1958 (Box 73, Folder 32)
    - Bard College, 1961 (Box 73, Folder 33)
    - Marcellus Hartley Gold Medal, 1964 (Box 73, Folder 34)
    - National Academy of Science, Public Welfare Medal, 1964 (Box 73, Folder 35)
    - National Medal of Science, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 36)
    - Presidential Medal of Freedom, 1964 (Box 73, Folder 37)
    - American Association of Physics Teachers, 1954-1974 (Box 73, Folder 38)
    - American Neurological Association, 1956-1963 (Box 73, Folder 39)
    - American Society of Mechanical Engineers, 1955-1967 (Box 73, Folder 40)
    - American Society of Science Writers, 1958-1960 (Box 73, Folder 41)
  - Speaking Engagements, 1957-1961
    - Speaking Engagement, Ben Franklin Stiftung, Berlin, 1957 September 19 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Speaking Engagement, Bucknell University, Lewisburg, PA, 1957 September 25 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Speaking Engagement, 13th National Electronics Conference, Chicago, IL, 1957 October 7 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Speaking Engagement, In-Service Institute for High School Teachers of Biology, 1957 October 12 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Speaking Engagement, Air Research & Development Command, University of Chicago, 1957 October 17 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Speaking Engagement, Dedication of Science Bldg., Hood College, Frederick, MD, 1957 October 18 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Speaking Engagement, Seagram Symposium, 1957 November 22 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Speaking Engagement, Hall of Fame, 1957 December 1 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Speaking Engagement, International Business Machines Corp., Opening of "World of Numbers", 1957 December 12 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Speaking Engagement, Japan Society, 1957 December 13 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Speaking Engagement, International Ben Franklin Society Annual Luncheon, 1958 January 18 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Speaking Engagement, Conference of Abstracting and Indexing Services, Philadelphia, 1958 January 29 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Speaking Engagement, American Chemical Society, Philadelphia, 1958 February 5 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Speaking Engagement, American Medical Association, Chicago, 1958 February 9 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Speaking Engagement, American Institute of Mining, Metallurgical & Petroleum Engineers, Inc., 1958 February 17 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Speaking Engagement, University Club Dinner, New York City, 1958 February 18 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Speaking Engagement, University of California, Berkeley, 1958 March (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Speaking Engagement, Association of Johns Hopkins Alumni Dinner Award, New York City, 1958 April 11 (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Speaking Engagement, Building Research Institute, Washington, DC, 1958 April 22 (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Speaking Engagement, Lord and Taylor Awards Luncheon, Citation, 1958 May 7 (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - Speaking Engagement, American Gastroenterological Association, Washington, DC, 1958 May 25-31 (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - Speaking Engagement, Lafayette College Commencement, 1958 June 6 (Box 74, Folder 22)
    - Speaking Engagement, Miami University Commencement, 1958 June 9 (Box 74, Folder 23)
    - Speaking Engagement, California Institute of Technology Commencement, 1958 June 13 (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - Speaking Engagement, International Scientific Radio Union, 1958 July 7 (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - Speaking Engagement, Mount Desert Larger Parish, Seal Harbor, ME, 1958 August 4 (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - Speaking Engagement, International Congress of Radiation Research, Burlington, VT, 1958 August 10-16 (Box 74, Folder 27)
    - Speaking Engagement, "Business Speaks" Gold Awards Dinner, New York City, 1958 October 9 (Box 74, Folder 28)
    - Speaking Engagement, International Conference on Scientific Information, Washington, DC, 1958 November (Box 74, Folder 29)
    - Speaking Engagement, Pomona College Dedication Ceremonies, Claremont, CA, 1958 December 6 (Box 74, Folder 30)
    - Speaking Engagement, University of PA, President's Luncheon for Chemical Industry, 1958 December 11 (Box 74, Folder 31)
    - Speaking Engagement, New York Academy of Science, 1959 January 8 (Box 74, Folder 32)
    - Speaking Engagement, Stanford University, Dedication of Biophysics Lab, 1959 January 10 (Box 74, Folder 33)
    - Speaking Engagement, American Institute of Electrical Engineers, 1959 February 4 (Box 74, Folder 34)
    - Speaking Engagement, University of PA, 75th Anniversary of the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1959 March 10 (Box 74, Folder 35)
    - Speaking Engagement, La Jolla Charter Day, Scripps Institute, La Jolla, CA, 1959 March 21 (Box 74, Folder 36)
    - Speaking Engagement, New School, 25th Anniversary Dinner, 1959 April 6 (Box 74, Folder 37)
    - Speaking Engagement, Kenyon College Lecture, 1959 April 13 (Box 74, Folder 38)
    - Speaking Engagement, Wistar Institute Symposium, Philadelphia, 1959 April 17 (Box 74, Folder 39)
    - Speaking Engagement, Hahnemann Medical College Commencement, Philadelphia, 1959 June (Box 74, Folder 40)
    - Speaking Engagement, Industry Day, New York City, 1959 July 28 (Box 74, Folder 41)
    - Speaking Engagement, Life Insurance Symposium, 1959 July 28 (Box 74, Folder 42)
    - Speaking Engagement, Radio Program WBZ, Boston, 1959 October 6 (Box 74, Folder 43)
    - Speaking Engagement, Bronx High School of Science, Dedication, 1959 October 27 (Box 74, Folder 44)
    - Speaking Engagement, American Academy of American Poets, 1959 November 4 (Box 74, Folder 45)
    - Speaking Engagement, Edison Foundation Conference, Washington, DC, 1959 November 5 (Box 74, Folder 46)
    - Speaking Engagement, Voice of America: "Education in the Sciences", 1959 November 17 (Box 74, Folder 47)
    - Speaking Engagement, Foundations Group Luncheon, New York City, 1959 November 24 (Box 74, Folder 48)
    - Speaking Engagement, Annual Meeting of the Association of Graduate Schools, 1959 (Box 74, Folder 49)
    - Speaking Engagement, Dedication of the Mental Health Research Institute, University of Michigan, 1960 January 29 (Box 74, Folder 50)
    - Speaking Engagement, "U.S. News & World Report" Interview, 1960 January (Box 74, Folder 51)
    - Speaking Engagement, The Bampton Lectures in America, Columbia University, 1960 February 23-25 (Box 74, Folder 52)
    - Speaking Engagement, New York Medical College Centennial Dinner, 1960 April 18 (Box 74, Folder 53)
    - Speaking Engagement, Super Market Institute, Inc., 1960 May 2 (Box 74, Folder 54)
    - Speaking Engagement, Louis H. Bauer Lecture, Aerospace Medical Association, 1960 May 9 (Box 74, Folder 55)
    - Speaking Engagement, Missouri Botanical Garden, Dedication of Climatron, St. Louis, 1960 October 1 (Box 74, Folder 56)
    - Speaking Engagement, Association of Military Surgeons, Washington, DC, 1960 October 31 (Box 74, Folder 57)
    - Speaking Engagement, Gideon Seymour Lecture, University of Minnesota, 1960 November 20 (Box 74, Folder 58)
    - Speaking Engagement, John F. Anderson Lecture, University of Virginia, 1960 December 5 (Box 74, Folder 59)
    - Speaking Engagement, American Rocket Society, Washington, DC, 1960 December 7 (Box 74, Folder 60)
    - Speaking Engagement, Symposium on Science and Food, Washington, DC, 1960 December 8 (Box 74, Folder 61)
    - Speaking Engagement, Mellon Institute, Robert Kennedy Memorial Lecture, Pittsburgh, PA, 1960 December 15 (Box 74, Folder 62)
    - Speaking Engagement, Highway Research Board, Washington, DC, 1961 January 11 (Box 74, Folder 63)
    - Speaking Engagement, Duke University Faculty Club, Durham, NC, 1961 January 12 (Box 74, Folder 64)
    - Speaking Engagement, Engineers Joint Council Annual Dinner, New York City, 1961 January 19 (Box 74, Folder 65)
    - Speaking Engagement, Goddard Space Flight Center, Greenbelt, MD, 1961 March 16 (Box 74, Folder 66)
    - Speaking Engagement, Trinity College Science Symposium, Hartford, CT, 1961 March 18 (Box 74, Folder 67)
    - Speaking Engagement, MIT Centennial, Cambridge, Mass, 1961 April 3-9 (Box 74, Folder 68)
    - Speaking Engagement, Temple University Convocation, 1961 April 11 (Box 74, Folder 69)
    - Speaking Engagement, Animal Medical Center, New York City, 1961 April 17 (Box 74, Folder 70)
    - Speaking Engagement, Hamilton College Commencement, 1961 June 4 (Box 74, Folder 71)
    - Speaking Engagement, Cancer Research Institute, New England Deaconess Hospital, Boston, MA, 1961 June 20 (Box 74, Folder 72)
    - Speaking Engagement, University of Colorado, Summer Lecture Series, 1961 June 26 (Box 74, Folder 73)
  - Speaking Engagements, 1951-1957
    - Speaking Engagement, Industrial Research Institute Medal Dinner, 1951 May 15 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Speaking Engagement, Washington Academy of Sciences, 1951 November 15 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Speaking Engagement, Basil O'Connor's 60th Birthday Dinner, 1952 January 7 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Speaking Engagement, Phi Kappa Psi Centennial Banquet, Philadelphia, 1952 February 19 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Speaking Engagement, American Society for Testing Materials, 1952 June 25 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Speaking Engagement, Brookhaven National Labs, Cosmotron Dedication, 1952 December 15 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Speaking Engagement, Colby College Convocation, 1953 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Speaking Engagement, University of Notre Dame Commencement, 1953 June 7 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Speaking Engagement, John Thomson Dorrance Laboratory, MIT, Boston, 1953 June (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Speaking Engagement, Charles H. Best Medical Research Institute, Dedication, Toronto, 1953 September 16 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Speaking Engagement, Indiana University School of Medicine, 50th Anniv, 1953 September 29 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Speaking Engagement, Brandeis Ceremony, 1953 October (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Speaking Engagement, Industrial College of the Armed Forces, Washington, DC, 1953 October 26 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Speaking Engagement, 4th American Forest Congress, Washington, DC, 1953 October 29 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Speaking Engagement, New York Academy of Medicine, Conference on Mental Diseases, 1953 November 5-6 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Speaking Engagement, Brick Presbyterian Church, New York City, 1953 November 22 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Speaking Engagement, Advertising Club of Baltimore, "Man of the Year Award", 1953 December 9 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Speaking Engagement, National Science Foundation, 1953 February 10 (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - Speaking Engagement, Symposium on Living Mechanisms, Metropolitan Long Island Subsection of the New York Section of the American Chemical Society, 1954 March 12 (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Speaking Engagement, Boston University Founder's Day, Boston, 1954 March 16 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Speaking Engagement, College of Physicians and Surgeons, Columbia University, 1954 March 20 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Speaking Engagement, National Health Council, New York, 1954 March 24 (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Speaking Engagement, National Science Teachers Association, Chicago, 1954 April 2 (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - Speaking Engagement, Kober Medal Presentation to H.S. Gasser, ASA, 1954 April 29 (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - Speaking Engagement, Kresge Research Institute, University of Michigan, 1954 May 15 (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - Speaking Engagement, Mills College Commencement, Oakland, CA, 1954 June 6 (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - Speaking Engagement, Medical Library Association Banquet, Washington, DC, 1954 January 18 (Box 75, Folder 27)
    - Speaking Engagement, Woods Hole Oceanographic Institute, Dedication of Lab, 1954 June 21 (Box 75, Folder 28)
    - Speaking Engagement, University of PA Hospital, 60th Anniversary, 1954 October 4 (Box 75, Folder 29)
    - Speaking Engagement, Physicians & Surgeons Conference on Religion & Medicine, Columbia University, 1954 October 16 (Box 75, Folder 30)
    - Speaking Engagement, Morgan State College, Baltimore, MD, 1954 October 27 (Box 75, Folder 31)
    - Speaking Engagement, Columbia University Bicentennial Celebration, 1954 October 30 (Box 75, Folder 32)
    - Speaking Engagement, Boston Society of Biologists, MIT, 1954 November 1 (Box 75, Folder 33)
    - Speaking Engagement, PA Conference of College Physics Teachers, Swarthmore, 1954 November 19 (Box 75, Folder 34)
    - Speaking Engagement, Philadelphia Academy of Surgery, 75th Anniversary, 1954 November 20 (Box 75, Folder 35)
    - Speaking Engagement, Washington Academy of Sciences, 1954 December 16 (Box 75, Folder 36)
    - Speaking Engagement, Greater Boston Chamber of Commerce, 1954 December 30 (Box 75, Folder 37)
    - Speaking Engagement, Army War College, Washington, DC, 1955 January 28 (Box 75, Folder 38)
    - Speaking Engagement, Churchmen's Washington Seminar, Washington, DC, 1955 February 15-18 (Box 75, Folder 39)
    - Speaking Engagement, Swarthmore Club of Greater New York, 1955 February 18 (Box 75, Folder 40)
    - Speaking Engagement, Cosmopolitan Club, New York, 1955 February 25 (Box 75, Folder 41)
    - Speaking Engagement, Forum on Democracy, Columbia University, New York, 1955 February 26 (Box 75, Folder 42)
    - Speaking Engagement, National Vitamin Foundation, New York, 1955 March 1 (Box 75, Folder 43)
    - Speaking Engagement, Riverside Church, New York, 1955 March 13 (Box 75, Folder 44)
    - Speaking Engagement, Society for Personnel Administration, Washington, DC, 1955 March 22 (Box 75, Folder 45)
    - Speaking Engagement, American Association of University Women, Troy, NY, 1955 March 24 (Box 75, Folder 46)
    - Speaking Engagement, University of VA, Founder's Day, Charlottesville, 1955 April 13 (Box 75, Folder 47)
    - Speaking Engagement, Delaware Academy of Medicine, 25th Anniversary, 1955 May 3 (Box 75, Folder 48)
    - Speaking Engagement, University of PA, Sigma Xi, 1955 May 18 (Box 75, Folder 49)
    - Speaking Engagement, American Association of Mechanical Engineers, Boston, 1955 June 19-24 (Box 75, Folder 50)
    - Speaking Engagement, Hospital for Special Surgery, Dedication, New York, 1955 September 29 (Box 75, Folder 51)
    - Speaking Engagement, Economic Club of Detroit, 1955 October 10 (Box 75, Folder 52)
    - Speaking Engagement, American Foundation, The Union Club, New York, 1955 November 15 (Box 75, Folder 53)
    - Speaking Engagement, Phi Beta Kappa Associates, New York, 1955 November 22 (Box 75, Folder 54)
    - Speaking Engagement, Philadelphia Patent Law Association, Philadelphia, 1956 February 16 (Box 75, Folder 55)
    - Speaking Engagement, New York University Club, 1956 February (Box 75, Folder 56)
    - Speaking Engagement, University Club, 1956 March 3 (Box 75, Folder 57)
    - Speaking Engagement, Engineers' Open House Assembly, Kansas State College, 1956 March 13 (Box 75, Folder 58)
    - Speaking Engagement, Priestly Memorial Award, Dickinson College, Carlisle, PA, 1956 March 22 (Box 75, Folder 59)
    - Speaking Engagement, American Philosophical Society, Philadelphia, 1956 April 20 (Box 75, Folder 60)
    - Speaking Engagement, Convocation of the University of the State of New York, 1956 May 4 (Box 75, Folder 61)
    - Speaking Engagement, Conference on Science And the Modern World View, Cambridge, MA, 1956 May 5-6 (Box 75, Folder 62)
    - Speaking Engagement, University of California Medical Center, 1956 May 29 (Box 75, Folder 63)
    - Speaking Engagement, Albany Medical College of Union University, 1956 June 1 (Box 75, Folder 64)
    - Speaking Engagement, MIT Commencement Day Address, 1956 June 8 (Box 75, Folder 65)
    - Speaking Engagement, Lake Forest College Commencement Address, 1956 June 9 (Box 75, Folder 66)
    - Speaking Engagement, Darthmouth College Commencement Address, 1956 June 10 (Box 75, Folder 67)
    - Speaking Engagement, MIT Conference on Acoustics, 1956 June 17 (Box 75, Folder 68)
    - Speaking Engagement, Danish Luncheon Club, 1956 June 20 (Box 75, Folder 69)
    - Speaking Engagement, Conference on Chemical Aeronomy, 1956 June 26 (Box 75, Folder 70)
    - Speaking Engagement, Conference on Future in Higher Education, New York University, 1956 September 27 (Box 75, Folder 71)
    - Speaking Engagement, American Association for the Advancement of Science, Dedication of New Headquarters, 1956 October 12 (Box 75, Folder 72)